Guide to the James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1892-1988; Series V; 1.67; (4 boxes)
  - Other Papers
    - Eulogy to JWJ by Gene Buck, 1938 (Box 92, Folder 750)
    - Notes and printed material relating to the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection at the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1940-1980 (Box 92, Folder 751-752)
    - Card announcing GNJ's death, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 753)
    - Commemorative stamp for JWJ and related ephemera, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 754)
    - Plaque with resolution by City of Los Angeles recognizing Jim Mapp and the Playward Bus Theatre Company for its production of God's Trombones, 1981
    - Business and Calling Cards, undated (Box 92, Folder 755)
    - Stationery, undated (Box 92, Folder 756-757)
    - French lesson created by JWJ for GNJ, undated (Box 92, Folder 758)
    - "The Subway Sun" broadside with JWJ quote, undated
      Published Now and Then by the Interborough Rapid Transit Company
- Printed Material, 1928-1973; Series VI; 0.83; (2 boxes)
  Arranged chronologically.
  Events Johnson attended as well as memorials in his honour are reflected in documents such as booklets, leaflets, programs, pamphlets, and other printed material. The series contains ephemera Johnson acquired when attending various conferences as both a participant and an observer. The series is also comprised of material documenting honours bestowed on Johnson such as buildings named in his honour and recognition of his birthplace in Jacksonville, Florida. Other printed ephemera such as a musical score and postcards, presumably collected by the Johnsons, are also included in the series.
  - Programs for events with JWJ, 1928-1938 (Box 93, Folder 759)
  - Programs for conferences in which JWJ participated
    - League for Independent Political Action, 1929 (Box 93, Folder 760)
    - The National Seminar of Jews, Catholics, Protestants, 1932 (Box 93, Folder 761)
    - National Conference on Fundamental Problems in the Education of Negroes, 1934 (Box 93, Folder 762)
    - World Conference on Church, Community, and State, 1937 (Box 93, Folder 763)
  - Programs for JWJ Memorials, 1938-1943 (Box 93, Folder 764-765)
  - Programs, brochures, and other ephemera collected by JWJ and GNJ, 1920-1977 (Box 93, Folder 766-773)
    Includes material with reference to JWJ and GNJ collected by GNJ following JWJ's death.
  - Issues of The Crisis with articles about JWJ, 1938-1940, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 774)
  - The Stage with article about Bert Williams and note by GNJ, 1936 August
  - Poster for Negro History Week with a portrait of JWJ, 1949 (Box 94, Folder 775)
  - Annual Report of the General Education Board (New York), 1945 (Box 94, Folder 776)
  - Eighth Report of the Senate Investigating Committee on Education (State of California), 1951 (Box 94, Folder 777)
  - Score for "The Bells" by Charles Taylor, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 778)
  - Program for Founder's Day Program at Hampton Institute, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 779)
    Includes address by August Heckscher at the dedication of a section of the Communications Center as the James Weldon Johnson Wing.
  - Booklets for James Weldon Johnson Celebration at Hampton Institute, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 780)
  - Booklets for City of Jacksonville (Florida) sesquicentennial, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 781)
    Includes photograph of sign commemorating JWJ's birthplace and of the James Weldon Johnson Committee with the Mayor.
  - Catalogue for exhibition on JWJ at the National Portrait Gallery, Smithsonian Institution, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 782)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 94, Folder 783)
- Legal and Financial Records, 1906-1998; Series VII; 1.46; (4 boxes)
  The series is organized into three subseries: Bank Accounts; Royalty Statements and Permissions; and Other Legal and Financial Documents.
  The series contains various documents representing the business aspects of Johnson's writing career, such as royalty agreements and statements, copyright certificates, and permissions. In particular the estate of James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson, which contains correspondence and the majority of royalty agreements, illustrates the legal complexities involved in managing Johnson's legacy. The estate's relationship with various publishers, such as Harcourt Brace Jovanovich and Penguin Books, is documented in various royalty agreements and statements. Royalty statements also reflect publishing fluctuations of Johnson's writings with particular emphasis on the 1980s and 1990s. In addition the series includes vital records relating to the Johnsons and documents pertaining to their properties. For example, the series includes Grace Nail Johnson's confirmation certificate and death certificate.
  - Bank Accounts
    - Account Books, 1938-1980 (Box 95, Folder 784-788)
    - Cancelled checks, 1928-1929; 1953-1972 (Box 95, Folder 789)
  - Royalty Statements and Permissions
    - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1985-1997 (Box 95, Folder 790)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers, 1982-1998 (Box 95, Folder 791-794)
    - Atheneum Publishers, 1968-1972 (Box 96, Folder 795)
    - Da Capo Press, 1989-1995 (Box 96, Folder 796)
    - Edward B. Marks Music Company, 1987-1995 (Box 96, Folder 797)
    - Estates of James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson, 1914-1995, undated (Box 96, Folder 798-802)
      Includes correspondence, royalty agreements (photocopies and originals), copyright certificates, and bank statements
    - Estates of James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson, 1914-1995, undated (Box 97, Folder 803-804)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1983-1995 (Box 97, Folder 805)
    - Macmillan Publishing Company, 1985-1993 (Box 97, Folder 806)
    - Penguin Books USA, Inc., 1982-1997 (Box 97, Folder 807-811)
  - Other Legal and Financial Documents
    - Abstract of Title, 1913 (Box 98, Folder 812)
    - Easement regarding property in Great Barrington, Massachusetts, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 813)
    - Copies of Grace Nail Johnson's record of confirmation and death certificate, 1966, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 814)
    - Bills and receipts, 1906-1932 (Box 98, Folder 815)
    - Leases, 1967, undated (Box 98, Folder 816)
    - Insurance, 1925 (Box 98, Folder 817)
    - Treasurer's book for JWJ Literary Club, 1918-1919 (Box 98, Folder 818)
- Family Papers, 1872-2005; Series VIII; 0.63; (2 boxes)
  The series is organized into three subseries: Johnson Family; Nail Family; and Ollie Jewell Sims Okala.
  The series contains an array of records, ranging from legal and financial documents to personal papers, representing the lives of the Johnson and Nail families as well as Ollie Jewell Sims Okala.
  The Johnson family is largely recorded through legal and financial documents, such as James Johnson's account books and bank books. The Nail family, and particularly John B. Nail and John E. Nail, is also represented. For example, John E. Nail's life as a successful businessman and prominent social figure is recorded in a scrapbook compiled by Grace Nail Johnson and Grayce Fairfax Nail.
  The Johnsons' close friend, Ollie Jewell Sims Okala, is likewise documented in the series. Okala's family life and education are recorded in material such as a yearbook, transcripts, diplomas, certificates, and a photo album. Okala's involvement in the Johnson Memorial Foundation, which she founded with Sondra Katherine Wilson, is also recorded.
  - Johnson Family
    - James Johnson's bank book, 1872-1875 (Box 99, Folder 819)
    - Account book for James Johnson's estate, 1913-1916 (Box 99, Folder 820)
    - Indenture granting Mary Barton cemetery plot, 1880 (Box 99, Folder 821)
    - Power of attorney granted to William Lighbourn by Ellen Johnson, 1905 (Box 99, Folder 822)
  - Nail Family
    - Baptism certificate for Edna Frances Miller, 1881 (Box 99, Folder 823)
    - Manual for Monthly Nurses belonging to Ellen Swain Robinson, 1884 (Box 99, Folder 824)
      Manual by Charles J. Cullingworth (Philadelphia: P. Blakiston, 1884)
    - Death notice for Polly Swain, 1892 (Box 99, Folder 825)
    - Certificates to John E. Nail from the Selective Service System, City of New York George Washington Bi-centennial Commission, and Real Estate Board of New York, 1932-1943
    - Certificate recognizing John B. Nail's membership in the Association for the Study of Negro Life and History, 1937
    - Certificate appointing Grayce F. Nail lieutenant of the New York Branch of the N.A.A.C.P., 1922
    - Mock proclamation to Captain Charles Young regarding menu, 1912 (Box 99, Folder 826)
      Signed by John B. Nail and W.E.B. Du Bois
    - Scrapbook about John E. Nail compiled by John E. Nail, Grayce Fairfax Nail, and Grace Nail Johnson, 1930-1942 (Box 100, Folder 827-834)
    - Obituary and notes about John B. Nail, 1942 and 2005 (Box 99, Folder 835)
  - Ollie Jewell Sims Okala
    - Yearbook, 1928 and 1934 (Box 99, Folder 836)
    - Photo album, circa 1930s (Box 99, Folder 837)
    - Preparatory Diploma from Philander Smith College (Little Rock, Arkansas), 1927
    - Diploma for a Bachelor of Arts from Philander Smith College (Little Rock, Arkansas), 1931 (Box 99, Folder 838)
    - Nursing Diploma and transcripts from Meharry Medical College (Nashville, Tennessee), 1934-1936 (Box 99, Folder 839)
    - Certificates, 1934-1942 (Box 99, Folder 840)
      Includes certificates licensing Okala to practice as a nurse in New York and marriage certificate
    - Insurance, 1991-1992 (Box 101, Folder 841)
    - Notes, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 842)
    - Printed material, 1969-1994 (Box 101, Folder 843-844)
    - Johnson Memorial Foundation, 1984-1993 (Box 101, Folder 845)
- Photographs, 1850-1985; Series IX; 5.96; (12 boxes)
  The series is organized into six subseries: Formal Portraits of James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson; Formal Group Portraits; Formal Portraits of Family Members; Candid Portraits and Snapshots; Portraits of Others Inscribed to Johnson; and Ollie Jewell Sims Okala Photographs. Many of the photographs were originally filed among general images in the James Weldon Johnson Collection. They were reunited with James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson Papers and arranged chronologically (within subseries).
  The series contains snapshots and portraits (both formal and candid) of the Johnsons and their family and friends between roughly 1850 and 1985. Many prominent photographers, including Irving Chidnoff, Theodore C. Roe, Carl Van Vechten, and Doris Ulmann, photographed the Johnsons and their family throughout their lives, as the formal portraits demonstrate. Johnson also received a number of portraits as gifts from friends, such as Nella Larsen and Alain LeRoy Locke.
  Various moments in Johnson's life are documented in the numerous candid portraits and snapshots, which include: Johnson's European tour with Rosamond Johnson and Bob Cole, his friendship with Paul Dunbar, his work with the American Consular Service in Venezuela and Nicaragua, his travels to Haiti and Japan, and work at Fisk University. Many photographs capture the Johnsons' relationship, ranging from early in their marriage while in Nicaragua and visiting family in Florida, up to the last photographs of Johnson before his unexpected death in 1938. Among the best-documented periods are the Johnsons' time at their homes in Nashville, Tennessee, and at "Five Acres" in Great Barrington, Massachusetts. These images portray the Johnsons surrounded by family, largely the Nails, and friends, who include W.E.B. Du Bois, Mary White Ovington, Bertha and Oliver Randolph, Walter White, Fania Marinoff, Carl Van Vechten, and Bert Williams. The exterior and interior of the Johnsons' home "Five Acres" is also heavily documented and includes images of Johnson's writing cabin. Photographs from the period following Johnson's death portray Grace Nail Johnson's recovery following the accident as well as her role at various dedication ceremonies and work to build the James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts and Letters at the Beinecke Library. The series also includes portraits and snapshots of Ollie Jewell Sims Okala, her family, and husband, Julius Byron Okala (Chukwunwike Etuka Okala Nwa-isi-nnwa Obi).
  - Formal Portraits of James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson
    Arranged by photographer or photography studio under headings for James Weldon Johnson, Grace Nail Johnson, and Art.
    The heading Art contains photographs of two-dimensional artwork portraying James Weldon Johnson.
    - James Weldon Johnson
      - Allen, James, circa 1920-1930 (Box 102, Folder 846)
      - Atlanta Photo Company, circa 1890 (Box 102, Folder 847)
      - Battey, circa 1904
      - Blackstone Photographic Service, undated (Box 102, Folder 848-849)
      - Chidnoff, Irving, 1937 (Box 102, Folder 850-851)
      - Patton Studio, circa 1920-1930 (Box 102, Folder 852)
      - Pinchot, Ben, circa 1920-1930 (Box 102, Folder 853)
      - Scurlock, George H., circa 1925 (Box 102, Folder 854)
      - Ulmann, Doris, 1929 (Box 102, Folder 855)
      - Underwood & Underwood, 1927 (Box 102, Folder 856)
      - Van Vechten, Carl, 1932 (Box 102, Folder 857)
        Includes photographs with Grace Nail Johnson
      - Unidentified, circa 1874, 1920-1930 (Box 102, Folder 858)
        Includes photograph of Johnson as child, at his desk in position of Executive Secretary of the N.A.A.C.P., and other portraits.
      - Various portraits reproduced in Along This Way, before 1933 (Box 102, Folder 859)
        Includes photograph of caricature by Miguel Covarrubias
      - Used in Fifty Years and Other Poems, circa 1921 (Box 102, Folder 860)
    - Grace Nail Johnson
      - Bachrach, circa 1900
      - Dummer, Oscar, 1886, circa 1890-1900 (Box 103, Folder 861)
      - Hargrave Portraits (New York, N.Y.), circa 1890-1900 (Box 103, Folder 862)
      - Marceau, Theodore C., circa 1900 (Box 103, Folder 863)
      - Pan-American, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 864)
      - Roe, 1909 (Box 103, Folder 865-867)
        Includes wooden frame made for the Johnsons by a sailor on their way to Nicaragua
      - Scherer, circa 1909 (Box 103, Folder 868)
      - Van Vechten, Carl, 1932 (Box 103, Folder 869)
      - Unidentified, circa 1900 (Box 103, Folder 870-871)
    - Art
      - Covarrubias, Miguel, undated (Box 103, Folder 872)
        Photograph of caricature of James Weldon Johnson
      - Savage, Augusta, circa 1938 (Box 103, Folder 873)
        Carl Van Vechten's photographs of bust of Johnson sculpted by Savage
      - Spingarn, Amy, 1930 (Box 103, Folder 874)
        Photograph of painting of James Weldon Johnson
      - Waring, Laura Wheeler, undated (Box 103, Folder 875)
        Photograph of oil painting portrait of James Weldon Johnson
  - Formal Group Portraits
    Arranged by subject.
    - James Weldon Johnson, Rosamond Johnson, and Agnes M. Edwards at Stanton Elementary School (Jacksonville, Florida), circa 1880 (Box 104, Folder 876)
    - "Atlanta University Quartette", circa 1893 (Box 104, Folder 877)
      Other members of the quartette include George Towns, Robert Gadsden, and Joseph Porter.
    - James Weldon Johnson with students as Principal of Stanton High School (Jacksonville, Florida), circa 1900 (Box 104, Folder 878)
    - James Weldon Johnson with Bob Cole and Rosamond Johnson, 1904 (Box 104, Folder 879)
      Includes various portraits including a photograph taken in their studio at the Hotel Marshall (New York City) and another photograph framed with music bars from well-known songs and signatures of all three men
    - "Dinner given by the American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers in honor of its President and Counsel Mr. George Maxwell and Mr. Nathan Burkan", 1914 November 29
    - "Citizens Club Banquet", 1915 January 23
    - "Beefsteak Dinner by the United Song Writers of America at Keens Chop House", 1916 March 29
    - "League of Small and Subject Nationalities", 1917 October 30
    - "Negro Silent Protest Parade", 1917 July 28 (Box 104, Folder 880)
    - "Meeting and Dinner of the Conference on Demobilization and the Responsibilities of Organized Social Agencies", 1918 November 30
    - "Honorary pallbearers at Bert Williams' funeral", 1922
    - Bon Voyage Party for Roland Hayes, 1925 (Box 104, Folder 881)
      Includes photograph of Walter Damrosch and James Weldon Johnson presenting Hayes with the Arthur Spingarn medal
    - Institute of Pacific Relations (Kyoto, Japan), 1929 (Box 104, Folder 882)
    - Dinner in Honor of JWJ, 1931 May 14
    - James Weldon Johnson with Fisk University students and faculty, 1931-1933 (Box 104, Folder 883)
    - James Weldon Johnson and Rosamond Johnson, circa 1937 (Box 104, Folder 884)
    - "International House Day Banquet", 1937 November 19
    - Meharry Medical College Graduating Classes, 1937
    - "Twenty-fifth Annual Dinner American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers", 1940 April 24
    - "Annual Dinner Meeting Song Writers' Protective Association", 1946 March 29
  - Formal Portraits of Family Members
    - Johnson Family
      - Anderson, H. and daughters Helen and Sarah, circa 1910 (Box 104, Folder 885)
      - Curtis, William C.H., undated (Box 104, Folder 886)
      - Dillet, S. Albert, undated (Box 104, Folder 887)
      - Edwards, Agnes, circa 1900 (Box 104, Folder 888)
        Includes photograph of her fiancee Dr. Darns
      - Johnson, Helen Louise Dillet, circa 1860-1880 (Box 104, Folder 889-890)
      - Johnson, James, circa 1910 (Box 104, Folder 891)
      - Johnson, J. Rosamond, circa 1873-1954 (Box 104, Folder 892-895)
        Includes photographs of Johnson with classmates, Taylor Gordon, and daughter Mildred; portraits by Carl Van Vechten; and photograph of letter from Chief Clear Sky of the Iroquois (1921 August 25).
      - Reynolds, Rebecca, circa 1950 (Box 104, Folder 896)
    - Nail Family
      - Braxton, Horace, undated (Box 104, Folder 897)
      - Braxton, James, undated (Box 104, Folder 898)
      - Braxton, Russell, undated (Box 104, Folder 899)
      - Griffin, Henry, undated (Box 105, Folder 900)
      - Griffin, Lottie Robinson, undated (Box 105, Folder 901)
      - Husk, Barney, circa 1900 (Box 106, Folder 902)
        Friend of John B. Nail
      - Johnson, Barrett and Catherine, circa 1900 (Box 105, Folder 903)
      - Jordan, Cornelia Robinson, circa 1890-1914 (Box 105, Folder 904)
      - Jordan, Gladys, undated (Box 105, Folder 905)
      - Middleton, Harry S., 1885-1894 (Box 105, Folder 906)
      - Middleton, Harriette Nail, circa 1900 (Box 105, Folder 907)
      - Miller, Edna Frances, undated (Box 105, Folder 908)
      - Miller, Frederick P., undated (Box 105, Folder 909)
      - Miller, Josephine Robinson, circa 1850 (Box 106, Folder 910)
        Daguerreotypes
      - Nail, Edward, undated (Box 105, Folder 911)
      - Nail, Mary Frances Elizabeth Robinson, circa 1860-1900 (Box 105, Folder 912-913)
        Includes cased photograph of Nail's childhood friend
      - Nail, Frank, circa 1888 (Box 105, Folder 914)
      - Nail, John B., circa 1860-1880 (Box 105, Folder 915)
      - Nail, John E., undated (Box 105, Folder 916)
      - Nail, Miss, circa 1890 (Box 105, Folder 917)
        Unidentified sister of John B. Nail
      - Robinson, Ellen and James, undated (Box 105, Folder 918-919)
        Includes cased tintype
    - Unidentified
      - Unidentified, circa 1880-1930 (Box 107, Folder 920-922)
  - Candid Portraits and Snapshots
    - James Weldon Johnson and Paul Dunbar, circa 1900 (Box 108, Folder 923)
    - James Weldon Johnson, Rosamond Johnson, and Bob Cole in Paris and with unidentified friends, circa 1905 (Box 108, Folder 924)
    - Grace Nail Johnson, Mary Frances Elizabeth Robinson Nail, Horace Braxton, and others, circa 1900 (Box 108, Folder 925)
    - Interior of Judge Matthews' Library, Albany, New York, 1906 (Box 108, Folder 926)
    - James Weldon Johnson visiting family in Jacksonville, Florida, 1909 (Box 108, Folder 927-928)
    - James Weldon Johnson, unidentified location, circa 1910 (Box 108, Folder 929)
    - American Consulate in Venezuela, 1910 (Box 108, Folder 930)
    - Johnsons in Nicaragua, 1910-1911 (Box 108, Folder 931-933)
    - Johnsons, and family in St. Augustine and Jacksonville, Florida, circa 1910 (Box 108, Folder 934)
    - Grace Nail Johnson and friends, Jacksonville, Florida, circa 1914 (Box 108, Folder 935)
    - Grace Nail Johnson and Johnson family, Jacksonville, Florida, circa 1914 (Box 108, Folder 936)
      Includes photographs of Sarah Anderson, Mildred Louise Johnson Edwards and her mother Nora Ethel Floyd Johnson
    - Various snapshots of Mildred Johnson, circa 1914-1917 (Box 108, Folder 937)
    - Johnsons and John E. Nail, New York, New York, 1915 (Box 108, Folder 938)
      Includes one photograph in front of Bert Williams' home
    - Grace Nail Johnson and family, Peekskill, New York, circa 1900 (Box 108, Folder 939)
    - James Weldon Johnson in Haiti, 1920 (Box 108, Folder 940-943)
    - Grace Nail Johnson and Nail family, circa 1920 (Box 108, Folder 944)
    - Grace Nail Johnson, Daisy Chambers, and Florabelle Pogue, Deep River, Connecticut, circa 1920 (Box 108, Folder 945)
    - Johnsons with friends and family at Atlantic City, New Jersey, circa 1920 (Box 109, Folder 946-947)
      Includes photographs of John E. Nail, Grayce Fairfax Nail, John B. Nail, Lena Tyers, Nettie Black, Mr. Alexander, Dr. Turner, A. Pope, Dorothy Thomas, Amanda Remp, and Agnes Marion Edwards.
    - Johnsons with John E. Nail, Grayce Fairfax Nail, Bert Williams, and Charlotte Louise Johnson Williams, circa 1920 (Box 109, Folder 948)
    - Johnsons, John B. Nail, Frances Nail, John E. Nail, Grayce Fairfax Nail, Lottie Griffin, and Josephine Miller, Southampton, circa 1921 (Box 109, Folder 949)
    - Grace Nail Johnson with Birdie O. Bird, Irma Bird Lee, Sam Lee, Bertha Bauman Randolph, and Constance Ridley in Plymouth, Massachusetts, circa 1923 (Box 109, Folder 950)
    - Johnsons, Francis H. Warren and others in Colorado, 1925 (Box 109, Folder 951)
    - Johnsons, Mr. and Mrs. William Pickens, Mrs. Nina Du Bois, John B. Nail, John E. Nail, and Grayce Fairfax Nail at Mary White Ovington's home "Riverbank" in Great Barrington, Massachusetts, circa 1925 (Box 109, Folder 952)
    - Johnsons, Mary White Ovington, Constance Ridley, and Bertha Bauman Randolph at "Riverbank," Great Barrington, Massachusetts, circa 1925 (Box 109, Folder 953-954)
    - Johnsons at "Five Acres," Great Barrington, Massachusetts during construction, circa 1926 (Box 109, Folder 955)
    - Johnsons, Grayce Fairfax Nail, Marion Beasley, Bertha Randolph, Oliver Randolph at "Five Acres" before completion of construction, circa 1926 (Box 109, Folder 956)
    - Johnsons, Bertha Randolph, John B. Nail, John E. Nail, Grayce Fairfax Nail, and Josephine Miller, Great Barrington, Massachusetts, circa 1926 (Box 109, Folder 957)
    - Johnsons, Walter White, and John E. Nail, Great Barrington, Massachusetts, circa 1926 (Box 109, Folder 958)
    - Johnsons, John B. Nail, John E. Nail, Grayce Fairfax Nail, Brenda Moryck, Bertha Randolph, Clara Wood, Great Barrington, Massachusetts, 1928 (Box 109, Folder 959)
    - Johnsons, W.E.B. Du Bois, Nina Du Bois, John B. Nail, John E. Nail and Grayce Fairfax Nail, Great Barrington, Massachusetts, circa 1928 (Box 109, Folder 960)
    - Photograph album containing snapshots of Johnsons and Nails at Great Barrington, Massachusetts, 1928-1930 (Box 109, Folder 961)
    - Johnsons, John B. Nail, John E. Nail, Grayce Fairfax Nail, Brenda Randolph, and Oliver Randolph, Great Barrington, Massachusetts, 1929 (Box 109, Folder 962)
    - Grace Nail Johnson, John B. Nail, Grayce Fairfax Nail, and Josephine Miller, Mt. Everett, Massachusetts, 1929 (Box 109, Folder 963)
    - Institute of Pacific Relations, Kyoto, Japan, 1929 (Box 109, Folder 964)